<Tasks>
    <GetItem>
        <ItemId Value="3617335871"/>
    </GetItem>
    <UpdateItem>
        <ModuleFolder Value="G:\SteamLibrary\steamapps\common\Mount &amp; Blade II Bannerlord\Modules\BannerPigeon"/>
        
        <ItemDescription Value="BannerPigeon adds a carrier pigeon mail system to Mount &amp; Blade II: Bannerlord. Send letters to any lord, your caravan leaders, or even port cities to recall your fleet! Perfect for diplomacy, recruitment, and managing your clan efficiently.

New in v1.5.0:
• Searchable Lord List: Contact ANY lord in the world via a searchable lineup!
• Fleet Recall: Send a letter to a port city to summon your fleet.
• Consolidated UI: Simplified and cleaner menu options.

Features:
• Contact any lord remotely via carrier pigeon (Searchable!)
• Contact your own caravan leaders remotely
• Fleet Recall system for port cities
• Realistic Travel Time: Optional distance-based delays (pigeons fly across the map!)
• Conversation Queue: Never miss a response - letters queue up if you are busy
• Settlement Support: Contact lords whether they are in a party or resting in a town
• Prisoner Checks: Smart validation prevents wasting pigeons on imprisoned lords
• Economy System: Gold cost is paid to the local settlement owner (if applicable)
• Full MCM (Mod Configuration Menu) integration for easy customization
• Save game compatible - uses proper save system serialization

MCM Settings:
• Pigeon Cost: Adjust gold required per message
• Response Time: Choose between fixed days or realistic distance-based travel
• Pigeon Speed: Fine-tune how fast pigeons fly when using realistic travel time
• Location Toggles: Enable/disable in towns or castles
• Notification Options: Control response arrival alerts

Perfect for players who want to streamline diplomacy, avoid endless map travel, and focus on strategy rather than chasing lords across Calradia.

Compatible with Bannerlord v1.2.X+
Requires: Mod Configuration Menu (MCM) v5.10.2 or higher"/>
        
        <Tags> 
            <!-- Type Tag -->
            <Tag Value="Utility" />
            
            <!-- Setting Tag -->
            <Tag Value="Medieval" />
            
            <!-- Game Mode Tag -->
            <Tag Value="Singleplayer" />
            
            <!-- Compatible Version - Update this to match your Bannerlord version -->
            <Tag Value="v1.3.9" />
        </Tags>
    </UpdateItem>
</Tasks>
